This tragedy happened this morning in Tennessee, a state that has been spending incredible amounts
of time and money on making drag queens out to be the biggest threat to children's lives,
while completely justifying an obstinance to gun reform. But the bigger conversation here is the
reason why children continue to be methodically killed in school shootings. Legislators and the
NRA make money by people buying guns. So it behooves these governments to relax on gun laws.
It also behooves them to create new boogeymen that scare people. And for the people who aren't afraid
of those boogeymen, the government acts in such an incoherent and unwieldy way that it makes those
people afraid of the government. So they've got a twofer, two groups of people who they've created
need for guns. And those people are so afraid that they are willing to put their children's lives and
their own at risk over the protection of possessing guns. When what they really need is removal of
the people who have created the feeling that they need those guns.